version: 2
task_description: 'Teach the model how to recognize positive words.'
created_by: junaruga
seed_examples:
  - question: 'Which word is more positive between "abundant" and "excessive"?'
    answer: Abundant.
  - question: 'Which word is more positive between "aesthetic" and "artsy"?'
    answer: Aesthetic.
  - question: 'Which word is more positive between "agreeable" and "condescending"?'
    answer: Agreeable.
  - question: 'Which word is more positive between "believing" and "insisting"?'
    answer: Believing.
  - question: 'Which word is more positive between "brilliant" and "clever"?'
    answer: Brilliant.
  - question: 'Which word is more positive between "confident" and "arrogant"?'
    answer: Confident.
  - question: 'Which word is more positive between "constructive" and "destructive"?'
    answer: Constructive.
  - question: 'Which word is more positive between "forgiving" and "resenting"?'
    answer: Forgiving.
  - question: 'Which word is more positive between "humble" and "diffident"?'
    answer: Humble.
  - question: 'Which word is more positive between "helpful" and "meddling"?'
    answer: Helpful.
